Guide to the Women's Studies Program records, 1981-2008 (bulk 1981-2002) UA.25.41.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Administrative Materials, 1981-2008; 1
  - Newsletters, 1984-2002; 1.6
    - Fall 1999 newsletter (Box 5)
    - Pictures, 1999-2000 (Box 5)
    - Spring 2001 newsletter (Box 5)
    - Winter 2002 newsletter (Box 5)
    - Spring 2002 newsletter (Box 5)
  - Special Projects, 1987-2001; 1.7
    The Special Projects subseries of the Administrative Materials series contains files related to large-scale projects created or coordinated by the Women's Studies Program. These projects typically spanned over longer peiods of time than events or conferences (as described in the Programs and Events Series) and may have involved multiple meetings, produced reports, involved undergraduate or graduate students in various roles, or otherwise extended beyond the regular work of the Program. Included are correspondence, reports, drafts, memorandums, writings, articles, newsclippings, and other materials. Special projects include Curriculum Transformation, a series of meetings to review and consider the development of the curriculum of the Program; the Women in Science and Engineering project (WISE), a series of discussions among faculty, administrators, and others about the presence of women in science and engineering; the Anne Firor Scott House, a women's studies living group; and several others.
    - Focus program privilege, power, leadership, 1993-1995 (Box 20)
    - Focus proposal from women's studies spring 1995: Privilege, power, leadership (Box 20)
    - Gender/body/self: General body-self, 1993-1998 (Box 20)
    - Gender/body/self: Lee's writings, vitae, etc., 1993-1994 (Box 20)
    - Gender/body/self: Financial papers, 1993-1998 (Box 20)
    - Reconnecting project: Biddle Foundation grant, 1991-1993 (Box 20)
    - Reconnecting project: Thinking about ourselves house course, 1991 (Box 20)
    - Scott house: Set-up process, 1987-1988 (Box 20)
    - Scott house: Resident info, programs, meetings, etc., 1988-1989 (Box 20)
    - Scott house: Resident info, programs, meetings, etc., 1989-1990 (Box 20)
    - Scott house: Resident info, programs, meetings, etc., 1990-1991 (Box 20)
    - Scott house: Resident info, programs, etc., 1991-1996 (Box 20)
    - Scott house: "A short history of a small place" report from 1988-1991 on Anne Firor Scott house/Women's studies dorm (Box 20)
    - Scott house: History- update 193, 1993-1994 (Box 20)
    - Scott house applications (in multiple year, blanks), 1989-1994 (Box 21)
    - Scott house, Undated (Box 21)
    - Scott house: 1988-1989 applications and evaluations (Box 21)
    - Scott house: 1989-1990 applications and evaluations (Box 21)
    - Scott house: 1990-1991 applications and evaluations (Box 21)
    - Scott house: 1991-1992 applications and evaluations (Box 21)
    - Scott house: 1992-1993 applications and evaluations (Box 21)
    - Scott house: 1993-1994 dorm applications (Box 21)
    - Scott house: 1994-1995 dorm applications (Box 21)
    - Mentoring Project, 1989-1990 (Box 24)
      FERPA restricted until 2060.
    - Mentoring Project: Applications, 1989-1990 (Box 24)
    - Mentoring Project: Evaluations, 1989-1990 (Box 24)
      FERPA restriction until 2060.
    - Mentoring project, 1991; 2 folders (Box 21)
    - WARP: Readings, process paper, 1991-1992 (Box 21)
    - WARP spring papers, readings, and transcripts, 1992 (Box 21)
    - WARP financial project report, 1992 (Box 21)
    - WARP interim project report (originals), 1992 (Box 21)
    - WARP, 1992-1993 (Box 21)
    - WISE: W. and sci.- Cosen, 1991 (Box 21)
    - WISE: W. and sci.- Hughes program, 1989-1990 (Box 21)
    - WISE: Correspondence, 1990 (Box 21)
    - WISE: W. and sci.- Duke programs- gen., 1990-1991 (Box 21)
    - WISE: W. and sci.- Duke classes, dept., evaluations, 1991 (Box 21)
    - WISE: W. and sci.- Disc. Group correspondence, 1991; 2 folders (Box 21)
    - WISE: W. and sci.- Seminar- Correspondence with Putman, 1991 (Box 21)
    - WISE: W. and sci. seminar- general file, 1991 (Box 21)
    - WISE: Articles, 1991 (Box 21)
    - WISE: Project- Proposals and report, 1992-1996 (Box 21)
    - WISE: Project- Finances, 1992-1994 (Box 21)
    - WISE: Project- Participants, 1992 (Box 21)
    - WISE: Project- programs, 1992-1993 (Box 21)
    - WISE: Correspondence, 1993 (Box 21)
    - WISE: Report, Mar 1993 (Box 21)
    - WISE: W. and sci. correspondence, 1992 (Box 21)
    - WISE: Report, Jul, 1993 (Box 21)
    - WISE: Report, Oct, 1993 (Box 21)
    - WISE: Women and Science: A Duke University community initiative: Final report October, 1993 (Box 21)
    - WISE: Women and Science: A Duke University community initiative: Abstract, 1993 (Box 21)
    - WISE: Articles on women in science, 1993 (Box 21)
    - WISE: Discussion group report, 1993 (Box 21)
    - WISE: Project: Student group and proposal, 1993 (Box 21)
    - WISE: Women in science and engineering, 1993-1998 (Box 21)
    - WISE: W. and sci. correspondence, 1994 (Box 22)
    - WISE: An executive summary, 1994 (Box 22)
    - WISE: Faculty Curriculum vitae, 1994 (Box 22)
    - WISE: NSF: Model Material, 1994 (Box 22)
    - WISE, 1995 (Box 22)
    - WISE: Women in research universities: Harvard, 1998 (Box 22)
    - WISE: MIT study, 1999 (Box 22)
    - WISE, 1995-2001 (Box 22)
    - WISE: Student paper: Aubrecht, seminar history paper, 2000 (Box 22)
    - WISE: Student paper: Aubrecht, B., presentation, 2000 (Box 22)
    - WISE: Student paper: Cho, Inhi, on women in science at Duke, 1997 (Box 22)
    - WISE: Student paper: Franks, Suzanne, multiple ones, 1990, 1996 (Box 22)
    - WISE: Student paper: Meekhof, Alison, women in science, 1994-1995 (Box 22)
    - WISE: Student paper: Russel, Emily, Botany replacement data, 1990 (Box 22)
    - WISE: Student paper: Schultz, Peggy, Biologists and their graduate experiences, 1990's (Box 22)
    - WISE: Student paper: Subramanian, Banu, Objectivity and the sociology of knowledge, 1995 (Box 22)
    - WISE: Student paper: Subramanian, Banu, Factional disciplines, 1995 (Box 22)
    - Duke men's project: Men's project for campus equality: Z Smith Reynolds proposal, Jan 1994 (Box 22)
    - Duke men's project: Men's project for campus equality: Z Smith Reynolds proposal, 1995 (Box 22)
    - Women's studies core bibliography project, 1990-1992 (Box 22)
    - Women's studies core bibliography project, 1991-1992 (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation, 1990-1991; 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: Memos to participants, 1990-1991 (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: Oct 10, 1990: Introductory session (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: Oct 24, 1990: Teaching Scheme (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: Scheme of teaching statements, 1990 (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: November 26, 1990: Gender Schema (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: Schema of gender statements, 1990 (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: December 12, 1990: Influence discussion (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: Jan 25, 1991: Discussion of 103 (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: February 8, 1991: Discussion of sexuality and society (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: Participants' project descriptions, 1991 (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: March 22, 1991: Discussion of participants' projects (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: April 5, 1991: Notes (Gilligan) (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: April 25, 1991: Workshop materials (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: May 22, 1991: Workshop materials (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: June 24 Workshop materials, 1991 (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: August 28 Workshop, 1991 (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: Workshop influence statements, 1991 (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: September 13, 1991: Workshop (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: October 18, 1991: Workshop (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: November 6, 1991: Workshop (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: December 18, 1991: Workshop (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: "Notes from" paper, 1991-1992 (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: January 30, 1991-1992 (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: February 25, 1992 (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: April 7, 1992 (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: April 30, 1992 (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: May 28, 1992 (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: June 22, 1992 (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: July 13, 1992 (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: September 14, 1992 (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: October 2, 1992 (Box 22)
    - Curriculum Transformation: November 6, 1992 (Box 23)
    - Curriculum Transformation: December 11, 1992 (Box 23)
    - Curriculum Transformation: January 6, 1993 (Box 23)
    - Curriculum Transformation: January 27, 1993 (Box 23)
    - Curriculum Transformation: February 10 and 19, 1993 (Box 23)
    - Curriculum Transformation: March 26, 1993 (Box 23)
    - Curriculum Transformation: April 26, 1993 (Box 23)
    - Curriculum Transformation: May 20, 1993 (Box 23)
    - Curriculum Transformation: June 7, 1993 (Box 23)
    - Curriculum Transformation: July 6, 1993 (Box 23)
    - Curriculum Transformation: June 1993 (Box 23)
    - Curriculum Transformation: September 8, 1993 (Box 23)
    - WS grad scholars, 1991-2001 (Box 23)
    - Scholars activities, 1994-1995 (Box 23)
    - Scholars activities, 1995-1996 (Box 23)
    - Scholars activities, 1996-1997 (Box 23)
    - Scholars activities, 1997-1998 (Box 23)
    - Scholars activities, 1998-1999 (Box 23)
    - Scholars activities, 1999-2000 (Box 23)
    - Scholars activities, 2000-2001 (Box 23)
    - Scholars applications spring and fall, 1994 (Box 23)
    - Scholars applications spring, 1995 (Box 23)
    - Scholars applications spring, 1996 (Box 23)
- Programs/Events, 1981-2001; 2
  The Programs and Events series of the Women's Studies Program Records includes materials related to conferences, seminars, guest speakers, and other events planned and hosted by the Women's Studies Programs. Included are annual or semi-regular events such as the Faculty Seminar Series and the Graduate Research Conference (planned by and featuring graduate students in the WSP) as well as one-time events and series of limited scope. Materials include correspondence, budgets, flyers and publicity, planning documents, articles, drafts of proceedings, and others.
  Notable programs and events include the Graduate Research Conference, held annually; the Changing Patterns of Our Lives, a conference held during Duke University's sesquicentennial (150th anniversary of founding) in 1989; the lecture series and symposium held in honor of the Women's Studies Program's tenth anniversary in 1993 and 1994; and materials related to WSP funding speakers across the University who tied their event to women's studies in some way.
  The materials related to the major annual events are arranged alphabetically, then chronologically; the remainder of the materials related to one-time events are arranged chronologically.
  - Faculty seminar series, 1983-1988 (Box 5)
  - Faculty seminar series, 1988-1990 (Box 5)
  - Faculty seminar series, 1990-1991 (Box 5)
  - Faculty seminar series, 1991-1992 (Box 5)
  - Faculty seminar series, 1992-1994 (Box 5)
  - Faculty seminar series, 1995-1997 (Box 5)
  - Graduate research conference: Celebrating our work: Schedule, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Graduate research conference: Celebrating our work: Abstracts, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Graduate research conference: Celebrating our work: Call for papers, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Graduate research conference: Celebrating our work: Correspondence, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Graduate research conference: Celebrating our work: Budget, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Graduate research conference: Celebrating our work: Publicity, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Graduate research conference: Celebrating our work: Other, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Graduate research conference: Border Crossings, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Graduate research conference: Border Crossings: Preliminary announcement, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Graduate research conference: Border Crossings: Call for proposals, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Graduate research conference: Border Crossings: Budget, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Graduate research conference: Border Crossings: Correspondence, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Graduate research conference: Border Crossings: Abstracts, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Engendering knowledge: Cosponsors/budget, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Engendering knowledge: Art show, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Engendering knowledge: Bios, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Engendering knowledge: Call for proposals, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Engendering knowledge: Abstracts, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Engendering knowledge: Schedule/program, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Engendering knowledge: Publicity, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Engendering knowledge, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Engendering knowledge: Proceedings, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Engendering knowledge: Proceedings, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Engendering knowledge: Proceedings, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Engendering knowledge: Proceedings photographs, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Feminists in movement: Proceedings, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Feminists in movement: Program, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Feminists in movement: Publicity, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Feminists in movement: Cosponsors/budget, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Feminists in movement: Abstracts, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Feminists in movement: Plans/details, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Feminists in movement: Call for proposals, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Feminists in movement: Steering committee, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Feminists in movement: Outreach/community groups, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Women's works: Proceedings, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Women's works: Proceedings, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Women's works: Steering Committee, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Women's works: Programs, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Women's works: Arrangements, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Women's works: Publicity, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Women's works: Funding/budget, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Women's works: Call for papers, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Women's works: Abstracts, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Women's works: Lunchtime roundtables, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Women's works: Abstracts, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Women's works: Exhibit, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Bodies of knowledge: Steering committee, 1995 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Bodies of knowledge: Call for papers, 1995 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Bodies of knowledge: Publicity, 1995 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Bodies of knowledge: Fundraising/budget, 1995 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Bodies of knowledge: Arrangements/speaker, 1995 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Bodies of knowledge: Program, 1995 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Bodies of knowledge: Abstracts, 1995 (Box 6)
  - Graduate research conference: Bodies of knowledge: Performances, 1995 (Box 7)
  - Graduate research conference: Bodies of knowledge: Communications, 1995 (Box 7)
  - Graduate research conference: Bodies of knowledge: Proceedings permissions, 1995 (Box 7)
  - Graduate research conference: Inroads: Steering committee, 1996-1997 (Box 7)
  - Graduate research conference: Inroads: Call for papers, 1996 (Box 7)
  - Graduate research conference: Inroads: Publicity, 1996-1997 (Box 7)
  - Graduate research conference: Inroads: Communications, 1996-1997 (Box 7)
  - Graduate research conference: Inroads: Fundraising & budget, 1996-1997 (Box 7)
  - Graduate research conference: Inroads: Speakers, 1996-1997 (Box 7)
  - Graduate research conference: Inroads: Abstracts, Undated (Box 7)
  - Graduate research conference: Inroads: Programs, 1997 (Box 7)
  - Graduate research conference: Inroads: Arrangements, 1996-1997 (Box 7)
  - Graduate research conference: Inroads: Conference Evaluations, 1997 (Box 7)
  - Graduate research conference: Inroads: Proceedings, 1997 (Box 7)
  - Graduate research conference: Steering committee/planning, 1998 (Box 7)
  - Graduate research conference: Speakers, 1998 (Box 7)
  - Graduate research conference: Fundraising/budget, 1997 (Box 7)
  - Graduate research conference: Arrangements, 1997 (Box 7)
  - Graduate research conference: Publicity, 1997 (Box 7)
  - Graduate research conference: Programs, 1997 (Box 7)
  - Graduate research conference: Communications, 1997 (Box 7)
  - Graduate research conference: Proceedings, 1997-1998 (Box 7)
  - Graduate research conference: Steering committee/planning, 1998 (Box 7)
  - Graduate research conference: Speakers/call for papers, 1998 (Box 7)
  - Graduate research conference: Fundraising/budget, 1998 (Box 7)
  - Graduate research conference: Program, 1998 (Box 7)
  - Graduate research conference: Publicity, 1998 (Box 7)
  - Graduate research conference: Arrangements, 1998 (Box 7)
  - Graduate research conference: Proceedings, 1998-1999 (Box 7)
  - Institute: Brochure, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Institute: Correspondence and photographs, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Institute: Registrations, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Institute: Budget, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Institute: Evaluations, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Institute: Rosters, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Institute: Schedule, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Institute: Introductions, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Institute: Alice Kaplan's originals, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Institute: Joanne Passaro's originals, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Institute: Phillip van Vleck's originals, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Institute: Carol Meyers's originals, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Institute: Faculty, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Institute: Curriculum, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Institute: Reading list (basic and suggested), 1993 (Box 7)
  - Institute: Simpson fellows, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Institute: Publicity, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Institute: Maps, facilities, menus, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Institute: Graduate school, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Institute: Alumni affairs, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Institute: Co-curricular activities, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Institute: Planning documents, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Institute: Learning vacations, 1992-1993 (Box 8)
  - Institute: Evaluations, 1995 (Box 8)
  - Institute: Communications, 1995 (Box 8)
  - Institute: Introductions, 1995 (Box 8)
  - Institute: Coursepacks, 1995; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Institute: Faculty, 1995 (Box 8)
  - Institute: Co-curricular events, 1995 (Box 8)
  - Institute: Publicity, 1995 (Box 8)
  - Institute: Brochure, 1995 (Box 8)
  - Institute: Budget, 1995 (Box 8)
  - Institute: Planning, 1995 (Box 8)
  - Institute, 1995 (Box 8)
  - Papers presented, 1981 (Box 8)
  - Women's careers in energy workshop, 1981 (Box 8)
  - Yasmine Ergas: The Italian women's movement in a comparative perspective, 1981 (Box 8)
  - Today's women workshop series, 1983 (Box 8)
  - In the works, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Moscow knows no tears, 1984 (Box 8)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt centennial, 1984 (Box 8)
  - McKenzie project, 1984 (Box 8)
  - Tatyana Mamonova, 1984 (Box 8)
  - Jean Elshtain, 1984 (Box 8)
  - Frances Fox Piven, 1984 (Box 8)
  - Cheris Kramarae, 1984 (Box 8)
  - Elaine Showalter, 1984 (Box 8)
  - Pornography awareness, 1985; 3 folders (Box 8)
  - The next discontinuity conference, 1984-1985 (Box 8)
  - Choosing children, 1985 (Box 8)
  - Stale roles program, 1985 (Box 8)
  - Nawal Saadawi lecture, 1985 (Box 8)
  - Queen Noor of Jordan visit, 1985 (Box 8)
  - Women's history week panel, 1985 (Box 8)
  - Library exhibit, 1985 (Box 8)
  - Annette Kolodny, 1985 (Box 8)
  - Joyce Ladner, 1985 (Box 8)
  - Career conference, 1985 (Box 8)
  - Sara Ruddick visit, 1985 (Box 8)
  - Bernice (Bunnie) Saudler, 1985 (Box 9)
  - Kate Young, 1985 (Box 9)
  - Margaret Rossiter, 1985 (Box 9)
  - Posters, 1985-1986 (Box 9)
  - Sue Rosser, 1985-1986; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Women in the arts, 1985-1986 (Box 9)
  - Sylvia Glickman, 1986 (Box 9)
  - bell hooks, 1986 (Box 9)
  - Grace Baruche, 1986 (Box 9)
  - NC women writers series, 1986 (Box 9)
  - Trinity faculty women 1930-1985 exhibition highlights, 1986 (Box 9)
  - Trinity faculty women 1930-1985 exhibit catalog, 1986 (Box 9)
  - Posters, 1986-1987 (Box 9)
  - Women in arts symposium, 1987 (Box 9)
  - Shortlidge symposium, 1987 (Box 9)
  - 1987, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Posters/flyers, 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - Dagmar Celeste, 1988 (Box 9)
  - 1988, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - AAC Meeting, Gender Scholarship and Curriculum: Jean O'Barr Panel tapes, 1988 (Box 25, Audio-cassette UA25410001-CS-0003, Audio-cassette UA25410001-CS-0004)
  - 1988-1990, 3 folders (Box 9)
  - The Changing Patterns of Our Lives Sesquicentennial symposium: Faculty, students, letters of invitation for meals, 1989 (Box 9)
  - The Changing Patterns of Our Lives Sesquicentennial symposium: Registration correspondence, 1989 (Box 10)
  - The Changing Patterns of Our Lives Sesquicentennial symposium: Jean's file, 1989 (Box 10)
  - The Changing Patterns of Our Lives Sesquicentennial symposium: Arrangements, 1988-1989 (Box 10)
  - The Changing Patterns of Our Lives Sesquicentennial symposium: Briefing notes, 1989 (Box 10)
  - The Changing Patterns of Our Lives Sesquicentennial symposium: Budget, 1989 (Box 10)
  - The Changing Patterns of Our Lives Sesquicentennial symposium: March 03 events, 1989 (Box 10)
  - The Changing Patterns of Our Lives Sesquicentennial symposium: March 04 events, 1988-1989 (Box 10)
  - The Changing Patterns of Our Lives Sesquicentennial symposium: March 05 events, 1988-1989 (Box 10)
  - The Changing Patterns of Our Lives Sesquicentennial symposium: Press releases and articles, 1989 (Box 10)
  - The Changing Patterns of Our Lives Sesquicentennial symposium: Memo by Missy on centennial, 1989 (Box 10)
  - The Changing Patterns of Our Lives Sesquicentennial symposium: Programs, Undated (Box 10)
  - The Changing Patterns of Our Lives Sesquicentennial symposium: Packets, 1989; 2 folders (Box 10)
  - The Changing Patterns of Our Lives Sesquicentennial symposium: Photographs, 1989 (Box 10)
  - The Changing Patterns of Our Lives Sesquicentennial symposium: Rave letters, thank yous, other correspondence, 1989 (Box 10)
  - The Changing Patterns of Our Lives Sesquicentennial symposium: Proceedings, 1989; 2 folders (Box 10)
  - The Changing Patterns of Our Lives Sesquicentennial symposium: Proceedings mailings, 1989 (Box 10)
  - The Changing Patterns of Our Lives Sesquicentennial symposium: Exhibit catalog, 1989 (Box 10)
  - Contemplating feminism lecture series, 1989-1990 (Box 10)
  - Soup and sandwich suppers, 1989-1993; 3 folders (Box 10)
  - 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Women's lives and friendship symposium: Gilligan correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 11)
  - Women's lives and friendship symposium: Heilbrum correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 11)
  - Women's lives and friendship symposium: Henderson correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 11)
  - Women's lives and friendship symposium: Promotion, 1990-1991 (Box 11)
  - Women's lives and friendship symposium: Campus initiations, 1991 (Box 11)
  - Women's lives and friendship symposium: Programs, 1991 (Box 11)
  - Women's lives and friendship symposium: Follow up, 1991; 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Women in science, 1991 (Box 11)
  - Kristina Svensson (Shortlidge fund), 1991 (Box 11)